<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arseniy Kouzmenkov</title>
    <link>https://arseniykd.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arseniy Kouzmenkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:58:53 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arseniykd.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://arseniykd.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:58:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniykd.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can reach me through:
 Personal Email: arseniy.kouzmenkov@gmail.com School Email: kouzmenk@ualberta.ca Linked In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/arseniykd/  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects &amp; Competitions</title>
      <link>https://arseniykd.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniykd.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects  Vitabu: This was our CMPUT 301 project. Vitabu is an Android app that provides users with the possibility to lend and borrow books from other users. This project was done in a group of 6 people. The project was built using Firebase. You can view this project here. Arduino Air Hockey: This was our CMPUT 274 final group project. We made an air hockey game in C++ for the Arduino platform with a realistic physics engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Experience</title>
      <link>https://arseniykd.github.io/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:15:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniykd.github.io/experience/</guid>
      <description>Arista Networks Software Engineering Intern, May 2019 - Present. Vancouver, BC
During my time at Arista Networks, I worked in the Routing Team. I made a framework to add generic counters to event occurrences, improving information available when debugging
Upgraded old CLI output method to work asynchronously, improving stability at scale
WCB Alberta Business Analyst Summer Student, May 2018 - August 2018. Edmonton, AB
During my time at WCB Alberta, I have worked on automating their manual testing scripts using the CodedUI Test Automation framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://arseniykd.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:33:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniykd.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>B.Sc. Computing Science Honors - University of Alberta (September 2017 - December 2020) Scholarships &amp;amp; Awards:  International Student Scholarship (2017 - Present) International Advanced Placement Scholarship (2017) International Country Scholarship (2017) University of Alberta Undergraduate Scholarship (2018) Dean&amp;rsquo;s Honor Roll (2018)  Completed Coursework  Introduction to Tangible Computing I &amp;amp; II: The Honors introduction to Computing Science done in C++ and Python. Development done on the Arduino platform to develop good intuition about necessity of efficient algorithms and proper memory management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://arseniykd.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:09:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniykd.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! You have gotten to this page for a reason, and that reason is to learn more about me, so here goes:
I am Arseniy Kouzmenkov, a third year Computing Science Honors student at the University of Alberta.
For developing, I prefer to use C++ and C for larger projects, Java for Android development and Python for small scripts. I really enjoy system development and working with low level networking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>